this is like definitely don't do
this if I purchase a 10ml vile of
deonate for my trt it would last me
about four months uh on the weekly dose
of 125 per week would the rubber stopper
and the testosterone be good within that
time frame yeah definitely the the
rubber stopper when it comes to you know
pharmaceutical testosterone uh expiring
you know breaking down over time it's
not something that's going to like sour
and go off like milk would it's
something that would arguably lose
potency or potentially it could
hypothetically lose sterility I guess
but the real issue that guys are going
to have with long-term storage of
testosterone cypionate if they're not
following like the advice that we talk
about in this group is using too big of
a needle to punch a hole in the top and
compromising the airtight nature of the
vile doing that over and over again
could cause issues but yeah if someone's
going through a 10 mil vial of
testosterone using 125 milligrams per
week no way are they going to have an
issue with that rubber stopper breaking
down that would take multiple months
potentially multiple years to occur so
no not not a concern he also writes I
read that the carer all can dissolve the
rubber stopper over time plus if I use
ampules perhaps I can preload syringes
how would the storage process work in
those scenarios I guess the only
hypothetical problem for breaking down
the rubber stopper would be if you store
the testosterone upside down so it was
constantly pushing against the the
stopper which I don't know why you would
do that um the stopper wouldn't be
touching the testosterone because of the
air at the top so um I don't think that
would be an issue unless it was
potentially laying down for very long
periods of time um I do wonder if um and
I I mean this very respectfully to the
original poster if these kind of
questions are manifestations of anxiety
um when it comes to um storing
testosterone in syringes a lot of guys
do this particularly in Australia
because they're using the Bayer
preloaded primat testin syringes which
uh I guess a bit more convenient than
ampules because you can cap them but the
problem with ampules is once you crack
it open you've got a whole Mill that you
that is essentially become non-sterile
instantly and a lot of guys will have
the solution of you know storing this in
insulin syringes to then use for their
next injections I strongly advise
against doing this because this is what
will break the rubber stopper down in
the syringes that's what he's referring
to that's a real problem I may have
misinterpreted the question if that's
the concern very real concern I've seen
guys do this and send me photos because
they'll unknowingly do it if they're
like going away for a week or going away
for two weeks they'll just for some
reason they don't want to take their
vial so they'll preload a bunch of
syringes and you can see by the end of
it the oil becomes discolored in the
syringe because that preservative is yes
breaking down the rubber stopper and
potentially it's also breaking down down
the wall lining of the syringe so you'd
be injecting Plastics and all kinds of
crap into the body insulin syringes are
not like I know that there's a bunch of
clinics in the states that are selling
like preloaded insulin syringes of of
other stuff as well this is like
definitely don't do this maybe overnight
24 hours you could get away with it but
I couldn't think of a situation in which
that would be necessary if you're using
ampules it it's even not advised that
people do this because as soon as you
crack the amp it's not sterile so even
if you draw and then inject it into a
vial that has the potential to cause an
infection but if people are going to
store testosterone after cracking an
ampule which most people will because
they're not going to be pinning a whole
ampule at once because we talk about why
that's not a good idea the only way that
you can do this and it's still not
recommended but it's the best option of
all of them is you have to transfer it
into a sterile vial sterile vials are
easy to get a farm should be able to
order one in for you um you shouldn't
even have to find one online you should
be able to buy one from a pharmacy but
it needs to be transferred into a
sterile vial yes it's cumbersome to draw
and inject and load and so forth but
that's why we don't really recommend
ampules a lot of the guys in the UK will
use susten on because the ampules are
real cheap I guess if that's if that's
worth your time to do then that might be
a good option but that's the downside of
ampules but yeah don't store
testosterone in insulin syringes